Polar Storm is a action, science fiction, tv movie film directed by Paul Ziller.
When a piece of the massive comet "Copernicus" collides with the Earth, it knocks the
planet off of its axis and unleashes a disaster never before witnessed.
James Mayfield and his highly trained research team are
the only ones who can re-align the axis.
With his wife and teenage son in mortal danger, Dr.
James Mayfield calls on his crack research team to help realign the planet's
axis before the effects of the catastrophe are irreversible.
Dr. James Mayfield, played by Jack Coleman.
Cynthia Mayfield, played by Holly Dignard.
Shane Mayfield, played by Tyler Johnston.
General Mayfield, played by Terry David Mulligan.
President, played by Roger Cross.
Lou Vanetti, played by David James Lewis.
The Core is a 2003 American science fiction disaster film directed by Jon Amiel with screenplay written by Cooper
Layne and John Rogers and starring Aaron Eckhart, Hilary Swank, Delroy Lindo, Stanley Tucci, D.
Qualls, Richard Jenkins, Tcheky Karyo, Bruce Greenwood, and Alfre Woodard.
The film focuses on a team of scientists whose mission is to drill to the center of the Earth and set
off a series of nuclear explosions in order to restart the rotation of the Earth's core.
The film was released on March 28, 2003, by Paramount Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $74 million
worldwide with a production budget of $85 million.
The tone is thought_provoking.